Hoang Quoc Tran

PROFILE

I'm a CTU graduate specializing in Human computer interaction and someone who has always been passionate about visually pleasing aesthetics. As a designer, I aim to create interfaces with usability and users' needs in mind. As a developer I create interactive experience using technologies such as React, Typescript. Currently working at Mews as a FE engineer.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

July 2018 - July 2022

- Took part in the development of multiple platforms aimed at students and employees of CTU Faculty of Electrical Engineering.
- Worked with variety of different languages, frameworks such as JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React etc.
- Communication with project managers, designers and other stakeholders on a daily basis.

UX designer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

January 2019 - July 2020

- Redesigned multiple already integrated applications used at CTU FEE
- Designed parts of new platforms aimed at students of CTU FEE
- Practical use of UCD process

Lead UX designer | Centrum Znalostního Managementu

July 2020 - July 2022

- · Lead an UX team consisting of 3 junior members
- Created a light design system to be used in future designs
- Conducted several complex user researches
- Usability testing as a part of design process

Frontend engineer | Mews

August 2022 - now

- Developing a property management system for hoteliers
- Communication with designers, other developers, PMs on a daily basis.

EDUCATION

Bachelor degree - Computer Software Engineering | CTU FEE

October 2016 - June 2019, Prague

Master's degree - Open Informatics | CTU FEE

October 2019 - February 2022, Prague

hoang.t.q@seznam.cz +420 721 198 728 linkedin.com/hoangtq

SKILLS

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript,
HTML, CSS, Python, Java

Libraries and Frameworks

 React, NextJs, TypeScript, styled- components, zustand, redux, fp-ts, react-query

Design

· Figma, Adobe XD

LANGUAGES

- · Czech (native)
- · Vietnamese (native)
- English (C2 proficiency)

INTERESTS

- Football
- Bouldering
- · Chess